Guide to the Robert L. Bracklow Photograph Collection 1882-1918 (bulk, 1896-1905) PR 8
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Alland Purchase, 1
  - Subseries I.1: Alland Purchase: Negatives, 2
    - West End Ave. & 86th St. [or Columbus Ave. & 86th St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 561)
    - Windmill, Long Island [Bridgehampton (N.Y.)], 1908 (Item 562)
    - Wood road at 233rd St. Eastchester [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 563)
    - Riverside Drive photo gallery [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 564)
      This image also appears in Album 9, page 13
    - Old house, Dyckman St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 565)
    - From Morningside Ave. looking towards Grant's Tomb [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 566)
    - Grand Boulevard & 64th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 650)
    - Sign covered bldg. being demolished [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 651)
    - Billboards on top of building (theatrical) [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 652)
    - Last of Fernando Wood wall, Boulevard & 77th St. [and billboards] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 653)
    - 232 William St. [billboards] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 654)
    - Columbus Avenue streetcar and theatre bills [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 655)
    - From the window of 122 West 36th St. [billboards, etc.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1890 (Item 656)
    - 42nd St. & Times Square (Broadway), (billboards) [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 657)
    - Razzle dazzle [Fairgrounds] [], 1893 (Item 671)
    - Coney Island [People walking on beach & sitting in boat] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 673)
    - Coney Island [Bathers and surf scene] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 673)
    - [Gipsy fortune teller at Coney Island?] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 674)
      This image also appears in Album 1, page 44
    - Countess Habeba Gypsy fortune teller, Coney Island? [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 674)
      This image also appears in Album 1, page 45
    - Little Egypt, Coney Island [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 675)
    - On the Sands [Two girls in a boat] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1891 (Item 677)
    - Coney Island [people on the beach] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 678)
    - Buffalo Bill [at left and two of his Wild West boys before tent, Coney Island?] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 679)
    - Buffalo Bill Wild West Show, Coney Island [Backdrop, log house, Indians & photographer] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 680)
    - Annie Oakley's tent, Buffalo Bill Show, Coney Island [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 681)
    - John M. Burke's Ranch, Pine Ridge, S. D. [log house and 2 men from Buffalo Bill Show] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 682)
    - Entrance to Greenwood Cemetery [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 725)
    - Monument/tombstone of Barney Williams [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 725)
    - Garibaldi Memorial, Stapleton, Staten Island [Staten Island (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 726)
    - C. Griffith tombstone, Greenwood Cemetery [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 727)
    - Lorelei Fountain, unveiled July 15, 1899 [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 728)
      This image also appears in Album 12, page 2
    - Lorelei Fountain, damaged March 25, 1900 [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 728)
      This image also appears in Album 12, page 8
    - Lorelei Fountain, restored [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 728)
      This image also appears in Album 12, page 16
    - Lorelei Fountain, restored, distant view [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 728)
      This image also appears in Album 12, page 15
    - Lorelei Fountain, restored, close up view [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 728)
      This image also appears in Album 12, page 14
    - Lorelei Fountain, damaged, back view [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Item 728)
      This image also appears in Album 12, page 10
    - Lorelei Fountain, side view [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 728)
      This image also appears in Album 12, page 4
    - Horace Greeley statue, in front of Tribune Bldg. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1891 (Item 729)
    - Shanties, 62nd St. near Boulevard [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Item 775)
    - 62nd or 64th St. near Boulevard, showing small cottage of O. K. Bottling Co., No. 45 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Item 776)
      This image also appears in Album 16, page 16
    - 62nd or 64th St. near Boulevard, showing another small cottage with yard and fence [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 776)
    - East 51st St., showing old house, tree and fenced yard [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 777)
    - East 51st St., showing old house on rock with fenced yard [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 777)
    - N.E. Corner 123 st. and Boulevard, showing old cottage on rock [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 778)
    - N.E. corner 123rd St. and Boulevard, with man and horse in foreground [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 778)
    - Shanties, West End Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1890 (Item 779)
    - Old Lyceum Theatre, 4th Ave. & 23rd St. [Madison Sq. Garden tower beyond] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 825)
    - The Dewey Theatre, East 14th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 826)
    - Castle rock and shore, girls by the water [Marblehead (Mass.)], 1891 (Item 850)
    - Marblehead, Corinthian Yacht Club & Point [Marblehead (Mass.)], 1901 (Item 851)
      This image also appears in Album 18, page 22
    - Steamer "Block Island" [Block Island (R.I.)], 1904 (Item 852)
    - "Shinnecock" boat at Block Island [Block Island (R.I.)], 1904 (Item 852)
    - "Waiting room" Marblehead, Mass., 1898 [bench between trees, men climbing trees] [Marblehead (Mass.)] (Item 854)
    - Marblehead. [Town over water & Schooner "A. P. Emerson, New York"] [Marblehead (Mass.)] (Item 855)
    - B.B.P's House [5 people on steps] [], 1889 (Item 856)
    - Malone Street, Jersey City [Jersey City (N.J.)], 1890 (Item 857)
    - [Old house or blacksmith out in the country] [], 1889 (Item 859)
    - Street and houses in Marblehead, Mass. [Marblehead (Mass.)], 1901 (Item 860)
      This image also appears in Album 18, page 5
    - Inwood Presbyterian Church [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 861)
    - House at Fort Lee [Fort Lee (N.J.)] (Item 862)
    - Van Cortland Mansion [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 863)
    - Van Cortlandt Mansion close up [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 863)
    - Gathering salt hay [], 1897 (Item 864)
    - Gathering salt hay [], 1897 (Item 864)
    - Snedeker House, New Lots, Brooklyn [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 865)
    - Eastern Yacht Club House [], 1892 (Item 866)
    - Gregory Street, Marblehead, Mass. [Marblehead (Mass.)], 1901 (Item 867)
      This image also appears in Album 18, page 8
    - Marblehead, Mass., waterfront scene [Marblehead (Mass.)] (Item 868)
    - American house, four story frame hotel with three balconies [] (Item 869)
    - [Woman standing on front porch of house with baby carriage] [], 1891 (Item 870)
    - [Chain bridge in ?] [] (Item 871)
    - Asbury Park, N. J., 4th of July, 1896 [Asbury Park (N.J.)] (Item 872)
    - Four children on a street in Provincetown [Provincetown (Mass.)] (Item 873)
      print made from damaged negative that was discarded
    - New Rochelle waterfront at Hudson Park [New Rochelle (N.Y.)] (Item 874)
    - [Oxen team, driven by a man] Clinton CT [Clinton (Conn.)] (Item 875)
    - Street scene, Clinton, CT [Clinton (Conn.)] (Item 876)
    - Asbury Park Beach [Asbury Park (N.J.)], 1896 (Item 877)
    - Clinton, Conn. Village street with load of hay pulled by ox team, bicycles, etc. [Clinton (Conn.)], 1899 (Item 878)
    - Marblehead Neck, Groups of people on the beach [Marblehead (Mass.)] (Item 879)
    - Massachusetts State House [Boston (Mass.)], 1899 (Item 880)
    - Harper's Ferry, Va. [Harpers Ferry (W. Va.)] (Item 881)
    - Marker, "Boston 8 Miles 1734" [] (Item 881)
    - At the cemetery [woman] [] (Item 882)
    - Massachusetts State House [Boston (Mass.)], 1899 (Item 883)
    - Harper's Ferry, Va. [Harpers Ferry (W. Va.)] (Item 884)
    - Seated Lincoln memorial statue, Newark, N.J. Little girl sitting on his knee. [Newark (N.J.)] (Item 885)
    - Seated Lincoln memorial statue with child on each knee, courthouse ? In background, Market St., Newark, N.J. [Newark (N.J.)] (Item 885)
    - [Carriage driving two ladies near country estate] [] (Item 886)
    - Sign in front of Huguenot House [New Rochelle (N.Y.)] (Item 887)
    - Somerville, N. J. [The Somerset House] [Somerville (N.J.)] (Item 888)
      This image also appears in Album 26, page 4
    - Harbor scene [Marblehead or Provincetown] [] (Item 889)
    - Frog Pond, Boston Common [Boston (Mass.)], 1899 (Item 890)
    - Robert Gould Shaw Memorial, Boston Common [Boston (Mass.)], 1899 (Item 891)
    - Charlottburg Hotel, Charlottburg, N. J. [Charlottburg (N.J.)] (Item 892)
    - New Jersey Rail Road [Passenger train] [New Jersey] (Item 893)
    - Sea Cove [marine view] [] (Item 894)
    - Main Street [] (Item 895)
    - Decoration Day parade at Great Barrington, Mass. [Great Barrington (Mass.)], 1905 (Item 896)
      This image also appears in Album 22, page 23
    - Decoration Day at cemetery, Great Barrington, Mass. [Great Barrington (Mass.)], 1905 (Item 897)
      This image also appears in Album 22, page 22
    - The Green, New Haven, Ct [New Haven (Conn.)] (Item 898)
    - General view of Marblehead, Mass. [Marblehead (Mass.)], 1900 (Item 899)
      This image also appears in Album 17, page 17
    - General view of Marblehead, Mass. [Marblehead (Mass.)] (Item 899)
    - [Shore scene, Marblehead?] [[Marblehead (Mass.)]] (Item 900)
    - [Houses on a hill, one at the foot of the hill along a cobblestone road] [] (Item 901)
    - Walking through the Park [], 1890 (Item 902)
    - Sag Harbor showing Dutch style house, barn and modern windmill [Sag Harbor (N.Y.)] (Item 903)
    - ["Eben Bradbury drugstore" with "Thompson Pharmacy" above it] [] (Item 904)
    - Watching yacht race from a pavilion, Marblehead [Marblehead (Mass.)], 1898 (Item 905)
    - Two sea salts, Marblehead [men on a dock] [Marblehead (Mass.)] (Item 906)
    - [Group of two men and two women before a building] [Portland (Me.)], 1898 (Item 907)
    - [statue in a park] [] (Item 908)
    - Lobstermen in front of their shacks [] (Item 909)
    - Dutch colonial farmhouse [] (Item 910)
    - [House on hillside with cattle, bay beyond] [] (Item 911)
    - Phillipse Manor House, Yonkers with statue in front [Yonkers (N.Y.)] (Item 912)
      This image also appears in Album 27, page 2
    - Quaker's prayer house [] (Item 912)
    - Horses [] (Item 913)
    - Columbus Day parade, Madison Square. [Crowds, Broadway horse cars, street lighted with arc lamps] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 915)
    - Blackwell's Island [] (Item 916)
    - Two masted sailboat [] (Item 917)
    - Two masted sailboat in Hudson River with early N.Y. skyline in background [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1902 (Item 918)
      This image also appears in Album 7, page 20
    - [View of a church or cemetery chapel] [] (Item 919)
    - [View from the Hudson, New York skyline] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 920)
    - Unidentified church under construction [] (Item 921)
    - [Revolutionary] fort in park, with flagpole on rock [] (Item 922)
    - Stone castle [] (Item 923)
    - Manhattan Life Building, No, 66, Broadway. Vacant, with "To let" sign [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 924)
    - Burnham Mansion, 79th Street and Broadway [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 925)
    - Round brick single story building [powder magazine?] with stone above door: "Built 1755" [] (Item 927)
    - Two story unpainted colonial mansion in country [] (Item 928)
    - Statue of Channing with Newport round tower in background [Newport (R.I.)] (Item 929)
    - J. R. Senior dry goods store, 214-220 West 125th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 930)
    - Stone church on corner with three other church steeples beyond [] (Item 931)
    - One story saloon advertising F. & M. Schaefer Wiener Beer [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 932)
    - Henry H. Tyson's Fifth Avenue Market [44th Street and 5th Avenue] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 932)
    - Replica of Viking ship in Hudson River [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 933)
    - Dr. Hall's Prebyterian Church, 33 West 52nd Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 934)
    - Marble Collegiate Church, Fifth Avenue and 29th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 935)
      This image also appears in Album 8, page 20
    - [Crowd and team, back of reviewing stand] [] (Item 936)
    - Summer hotel [] (Item 937)
    - Corner saloon, "The Junction. G. Bergau" [163rd Street and Amsterdam Avenue] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 938)
    - Old commercial bldg. Holmberg Machine Shop and Blacksmith, "Jas. Gibbons & Son gas appliances" (upstairs) at 412 [?] St.; John Cusick next door at 413 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 939)
    - Corner of Battery Park and harbor with Castle Garden in right foreground [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 940)
    - Four Story Hotel Metropole with 9 story bldg. advertising Pabst on roof, next door. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 941)
    - Unitarian Church [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 942)
    - Suburban house, Bayside [Queens (New York, N.Y.)], [1890] (Item 943)
    - New York City theatrical signs [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 944)
    - New York City theatrical signs [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 944)
    - Old houses, one with basement sign, "L. Lipkind. Jobber in books. 35", [?] St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 945)
    - Reviewing stand, "Grand view stand. Tickets Stevens 93 St. and Columbus Ave." [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 946)
    - [View of New York from Hudson River toward Pier 13] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 947)
    - [View toward west on 49th Street. Old Columbia College building] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 948)
    - [Unidentified house with windmill] [] (Item 949)
    - Castellated mansions in suburbs [] (Item 950)
    - Jumel Mansion [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 951)
    - [New York skyline] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 952)
    - Tree lined suburban residential street with early autos. (very good shot) [] (Item 953)
    - Ericsson statue [] (Item 954)
    - East side of Varick Street, St. John's Chapel [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 955)
    - Lighthouse [] (Item 956)
    - Grant's Tomb, close up [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 957)
    - New York skyline from East River, showing old shot tower? [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 958)
    - Burnham Mansion [Broadway, between 78th and 79th Streets] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 959)
    - St. Paul's Chapel close up with porch decorated for Columbus Day [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 960)
    - Winter view of Madison Square park showing Dr. Parkhurst's church [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 961)
    - Water front trucking scene at pier 46 Troy Line. (All horse-drawn trucks) [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 962)
    - Broadway & Duane St. showing old bldgs. and signs, including "Geo. P. Hall & Son, photo" [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1890 (Item 963)
    - Close up of buildings on Blackwell's Island [Roosevelt Island (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Item 964)
      This image also appears in Album 11, page 17
    - Market Square, with modern fire house at left, old three story stores at right [Newburyport (Mass.)], 1896 (Item 965)
      This image also appears in Album 2, page 52
    - Duane St. Methodist Church close up, with 2nd hand furniture store in part of the church [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Item 966)
      This image also appears in Album 14, page 12
    - [Old mill house and tall tree] [] (Item 967)
    - 125th St. Viaduct, close up from below, showing construction [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 968)
    - [New York skyline from Hudson] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 970)
    - Street in financial section, looking towards East River (National City Bank at right, Wall St. east from west of William St.) [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 971)
    - Jumel Mansion from below. Good early shot [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 972)
    - Waterfront. Early view showing arc lights [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 973)
    - [Paterno Castle? Mansion on Riverside Drive] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 974)
    - Suburban mansion in winter [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1903 (Item 975)
      This image also appears in Album 13, page 11
    - [Two colonial cottages] [] (Item 976)
    - Long dilapidated Dutch colonial farm house [] (Item 977)
    - Madison Square Garden Tower from park, Seward statue in foreground, winter [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 978)
    - Three story apartment row with balconies, 7th Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 979)
    - Peter Cooper statue in front of Cooper Union [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 980)
    - Old two story shack [] (Item 981)
    - Sheep in Central Park [The Sheep Meadow] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1000)
    - Pabst Bldg., 1899 [under construction] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1001)
    - Pabst Bldg., 1899 [under construction, Frame only] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1001)
      This image also appears in Album 8, page 26
    - Hammerstein's Victoria Theatre [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1002)
    - Gotham, East 4th St., 1901 [2 old doorways, Old Merchants' House] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1003)
    - First Battery armory [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1897 (Item 1004)
    - City Hall, 1891 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1005)
    - [Looking north from South St., 1915] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1006)
    - South St. from Maiden Lane to Burling Slip [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1891 (Item 1007)
    - Poe Cottage, Fordham, 1896 [NOT Poe Cottage] [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1008)
    - Bronx River, 1895 [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1009)
    - Bronx police [Dutch farmhouse in background, cor. Borden Ave. & Laurel Hill Blvd.] [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1010)
    - Erie Office Bldg., West St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Item 1011)
      This image also appears in Album 14, page 16
    - Royal Insurance Bldg., 84 William St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1915 (Item 1012)
    - Royal Insurance Bldg., 84 William St. (opposite view) [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1915 (Item 1012)
    - Up Broadway, 1912 [Elaborate lamp of Berwind-White Coal Mining Co., No. 1 Broadway, Bowling Green in foreground] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1013)
    - Up Broadway from Liberty St., 1916 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1014)
    - Down Broadway from Post Office, 1916 [showing St. Paul's Chapel] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1014)
    - Boulevard & 96th St. or 68th St.? [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1015)
    - Boulevard & 96th St. or 68th St.? (opposite corner) [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1015)
    - East 53rd St., 1902 [Shot tower, 18 century house and sailboat at dock, "Bell Bros." sign] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1016)
    - ["Hippolyte Dumois", steamer at pier] [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1891 (Item 1017)
    - Central Park horse cars, 1892 [on Broadway between Post Office and St. Paul's Chapel] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1018)
    - 45-49 Convent Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1889 (Item 1019)
    - 716 Broadway, 1889 [Greek revival bldg., also No. 714 and 718] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1020)
    - New York University bldg. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1889 (Item 1021)
    - 28th St. curio shop, back of 5th Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1022)
    - 28th St. curio shop, close up [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1022)
    - Morningside Park, 118-119 Sts. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1897 (Item 1024)
    - [Statue of Daniel Webster, 1889] [] (Item 1025)
    - Hudson St. Hospital or "House of Relief, N.Y. Hospital", now U.S. Marine Hospital [67 Hudson St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1026)
    - Water St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Item 1027)
    - Broad St., 1904, showing new Stock Exchange [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1028)
    - Morningside Castle, 1890 [Old 2 story cottage] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1029)
    - Battery Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1030)
    - [Shakespeare statue, the Mall, Central Park] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1031)
    - [Street scene, Henry's Market, #475] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1031)
    - [Park, 1905], Manhattan Ave. at foot of Morningside Drive [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1032)
    - Germania Fire Insurance Co., 1909 [in distance. Old bldgs. with cigar store Indian in foreground in front of J. Cosio cigar store.) [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1033)
    - Germania Fire Insurance Co. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Item 1033)
    - 242nd St. & Riverside Ave., 1913 [Dutch colonial house in fenced yard] [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1034)
    - Brooklyn Bridge from East River & 12 St., 1891 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1035)
    - Riverside Drive [Cyrus Clark mansion] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1890 (Item 1036)
    - Ross Castle, Killarney, Ireland [?] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1037)
    - Castle [Ireland?] [] (Item 1037)
    - Ferry & Cliff Sts. [Bronze tablet on Schieren Bldg., site of the Old Swamp, tanneries.] [] (Item 1038)
    - Old Post Office below City Hall, 1891 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1039)
    - New York Clearing House [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 1040)
    - 92nd St. & 8th Ave., 1897 [Old house on corner] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1041)
    - Morse House, 5 West 22nd St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1042)
    - [New York Furniture Co. removal sale. In fine old mansion] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1043)
    - Bussing Homestead, 147th St., 1890 [Dutch colonial farmhouse] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1044)
    - Watts St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1045)
    - 90 Grove St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1046)
    - Market, Canal & Spring Sts. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1047)
    - State Street, Battery Park [old houses on north side] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1048)
    - [Andrew Carnegie Mansion, Fifth Ave. 90th-91st Sts.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1049)
    - Convent Ave. between 140th and 141st St. [one story shack under trees] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1050)
    - Koster & Bial's Theatre, 34th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Item 1051)
    - Canal St., 1891 [Old houses] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1052)
    - Jumel Mansion [from below] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1889 (Item 1053)
    - Hotel, Broadway at about 74th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Item 1054)
    - Y.M.C.A., 23rd St. & 4th Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1055)
      This image also appears in Album 9, page 6
    - Washington Bridge [Washington Bridge (New York, N.Y.)], 1891 (Item 1056)
    - Alexander Hamilton's 13 trees [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1889 (Item 1057)
    - [Anchor Line ship offices, corner of ] S. of Army Bldg. ["Star," Anchor Lines] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1058)
    - [Steamboat Row Nos. 1-9. North German Lloyd, French Line, Cunard, Clyde, Red, Star, Anchor line] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1058)
    - Grand & Centre Sts. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1059)
    - 239th St. & Spuyten Duyvel Parkway [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 1060)
    - State & Whitehall Sts. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1061)
    - Lafayette Place from No. 56 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1890 (Item 1062)
    - Teacher's College, 120th St. & Boulevard [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1897 (Item 1063)